Guide to the American Left Ephemera Collection, 1875-2015 AIS.2007.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Communist Party USA (CPUSA), VII.
  - "How Can We Share the Wealth?", The Communist Way Versus Huey Long, By Alex Bittelman, April, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "An Open Letter to all the Members of the Communist Party" (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Labor and Anti- Semitism", By George Morris, May, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor", By Karl Yoneda (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "The Meaning of the XXth Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union", Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, U.S.A., By Max Weiss, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Delegate, Special Convention Communist Party, U.S.A., July 4-7, 1968" (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Religion and Communism", By Earl Browder, June, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Talks to America", By Earl Browder, February, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Social and National Security", By Earl Browder, December, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "An American People's Program to End Poverty and Unemployment in the U.S.", Economic Program of the Communist Party, U.S.A. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Passage to Progress", The '64 Election Mandate and the Road Ahead, December, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "A Communist Talks to Students", March, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Youth Demands Peace", By James Lerner (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "The Philosophy of Communism", By James E. Jackson, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Invitation to Join the Communist Party", By Robert Minor, February, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "In Defense of the Communist Party", Guide for Study and Discussion of William Z. Foster's Pamphlet, August, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "The Truth About Father Coughlin", By A.B. Magil, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Policy for Victory", By Earl Browder, May, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Coal Miners and the War", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, August, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Life in the U.S. Army", By Walter Trumbull (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Youth Serves the Nation", By Max Weiss, February, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Youth for Victory in 1943", By Max Weiss, February, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - "Fight for Your Future Now!", By Max Weiss, November, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - "Peace or War, The People against the Warmakers!", By Eugene Dennis, May, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - "The Year of Great Decision, 1942", By Robert Minor, May, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - "The MacArthur Ouster", By Eugene Dennis (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "Intellectuals and the War", By V.J. Jerome (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - "Two Questions on Winning the War", By Roy Hudson, May, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - "The Trade Unions and the War", By William Z. Foster, June, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "What's What About the War", Questions and Answers, By William Z. Foster, July, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - "Quarantine the War Mongers", By William Z. Foster, November, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - "May Day Anti-War Rally" Flyer, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - "Make the Democrats Keep Their Promises", June, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - "Youth Confronts the Blue Eagle", By Gil Green (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Complete Schedule of Classes at the California Labor School (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - "How to Win Jobs!", By Leonard Sparks (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - "Labor and the Menace of Goldwaterism", By George Morris, September, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - "Industrial Slavery- Roosevelt's 'New Deal'", By I. Amter, July, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - "The Trotskyite Fifth Column in the Labor Movement", By George Morris, January, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - "Company Unions Today", By Robert W. Dunn, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - "Labor and the Marshall Plan", By William Z. Foster, March, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - "Reaction Beats Its War Drums", By William Z. Foster, May, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - "Smash Hitler's Spring Offensive Now!", By William Z. Foster, March, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - "Why Work for Nothing?", By Herman Schendel, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - "The People and the Congress", William Z. Foster, February, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - "Should Americans Back the Marshall Plan?", Joseph Starobin, February, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - "The Farmer's Way Out", Life Under a Worker's and Farmer's Government, By John Barnett, June, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - "Work for all or Unemployment" (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - "Illinois Needs a Farmer- Labor Party", By Morris H. Childs (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - "Industrial Insurance: A Snare for Workers", By Mort and E.A. Gilbert, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "How to Fight High Prices", By Louise Mitchell, November, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - "Where to Begin?", How to Build a Mass Young Communist League, By F. Fuerenberg (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - "Americans of Foreign Birth in the War Program for Victory", By Hon. Earl G. Harrison (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - "Reconversion", Security or Crisis, By Allan Ross (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - "World-Wide Unemployment", 20,000,000 Unemployed (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - San Francisco Conference Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Clarity, Notes on the National Question, September, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - "Schools and the Crisis", By Rex David, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - "Poverty 'Midst Riches, Why We Demand Unemployment Insurance" (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - "The History of May Day", By Alexander Trachtenberg (3), 1935, 1937, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - "May Day", 1886: 8 Hour Work Day, 1959:6 Hour Work Day (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - "Appalachia U.S.A.", A Study in Poverty, By George Meyers (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - "How's Your Health?", The Fight for a National Health Program, By Robert Friedman, February, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - "Broaden the Fight for Peace and Democracy!", By Joseph Rockman, September, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - "Fight! Don't Starve!", Demands for Unemployment Insurance Made Upon the United States Congress (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - "On the Struggle Against Revisionism", January, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - "I Didn't Raise My Boy to Be a Solider-for Wall Street", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, February, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - "Unemployment Insurance", The Burning Issue of the Day, By Earl Browder, April, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - "20th Century Methods!" Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - "A Democratic Way Out of the Crisis in Education", A Program for Resolving the Crisis in the New York City Public School System (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Educational Bulletin, March, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - "Your Questions Answered", On Politics, Peace, Economics, Fascism, Anti-Semitism, Race Prejudice, Religion, Trade Unionism, Americanism, Democracy, Socialism, Communism, By William Z. Foster, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - "Heroines", By Sasha Small (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - "Everybody Can Be Rich- and Still Be Honest!", The Bread-And-Butter Facts of Life, By Jim West (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - "What Price Profits?", By Max Weiss, April, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - "March for Peace May 1st 1952", United Labor and People's Committee for May Day (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - "The Real Father Coughlin", By A.B. Magil, May, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - "More Agitation, More Propaganda!, By E. Fisher (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - "Smash Michigan's Fifth Column!", August, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - "White Guard Terrorists in the U.S.A.", By Leon Dennen (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - "The Black Legion Rides", By George Morris, August, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - "Texas Survey" Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - "Here's to Health!", 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - "Hold That Rent Ceiling", By Louise Mitchell, January, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - "America's Housing Crisis", By Louise Mitchell, May, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - "The Fascist Revival...the Inside Story of the John Birch Society...Who is in it? Who is Behind it? Who Directs and Finances it?", By Mike Newberry, June, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - "How Mellon Got Rich", By Harvey O'Connor, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - "The Truth About the MTA", By Daniel B. Schirmer (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Sales, Tax is Robbery!, Mass Action Will Force Its Repeal (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - "The Elections and the Outlook for National Unity", By Eugene Dennis, December, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - "Where Do We Go From Here?", By "Americus", November 6, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - "The Watson-Parker Law", The Latest Scheme to Hamstring Railroad Unionism, By William Z. Foster, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - "This is Treason!", By Sol Vail (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - "Housecleaning by Labor, Not Housewrecking by Congress" (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - "The American Way to Jobs, Peace, Democracy", May, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - "Democracy in Danger", By Mary Collins, September, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - "The Case Against David Dubinsky", By William Weinstone, June, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - "Freedom Begins at Home", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, July, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - "The Menace of Opportunism", By Max Bedacht (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - "The Rankin Witch Hunt", By William Z. Foster, December, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - "Science and Life", By J.G. Crowther, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - "Is Anybody Pushing You Around?" (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - "The American Holiday, May Day 1939", By Jane Filley, April, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - "William Z. Foster, An Appreciation", By Joseph North, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - "I Challenge the Un-Americans", By Eugene Dennis, May, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - "My Side of the Story", The Statement the Newspapers Refused to Print, By Gerhart Eisler, March, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - "DEBS and DENNIS, Fighters for Peace", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, October, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - "Stool-Pigeon", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, July, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - "Food Prices and Rationing", By Louise Mitchell, January, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - "Jews and the National Question", By Hyman Levy, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - "Jews in Action" (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - "The Jewish People and the War", By Earl Browder, May, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - "The C.I.O. Today", By George Morris, March, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - "World Capitalism and World Socialism", By William Z. Foster, March, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - "The 'Foreign Agent' Hoax Exposed", April 4, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - "Hamtrack Municipal Election of 1934" Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - "In the Dungeons of Mussolini", By Carlo Rossi, March, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Peoples Educational Center Directory (Spring), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - "Facts About Gerald L. K. Smith", June 26, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - "Resolution on the Path to Native American Indian Liberation, December, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - "The Working Class and the Nation" and "Changes in Bourgeois Nationalism", By Peter Weiden, 1938, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - "It's You They're After!" (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - "The Foreign Born in the United States", By Dwight C. Morgan, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - YCL Pacesetter, August, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - "In Flanders Field...", By Mac Weiss, May, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - "Nazis Preferred", The Renazification of Western Germany, By Moses Miller, June, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - "Pattern for American Fascism", By John L. Spivak, September, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - "Post-War Jobs for Veterans, Negroes, and Women", By Roy Hudson, November, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Pamphlet About Reuben W. Borough (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - "The U.S.A. and the U.S.S.R., War Allies and Friends", By William Z. Foster, October, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - "The Fight Against Hitlerism", By William Z. Foster and Robert Minor, July, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - "The Menace of a New World War", By William Z. Foster, March, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - "The 'Free' Press", Portrait of a Monopoly, By George Marion, June, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - "New Program of the Communist Party USA", The People versus Corporate Power, January, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - A Pamphlet for the Communist Party Presidential Candidate Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner for Vice President (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - A Flyer for the American Youth Congress Citizenship Institute in Washington, D.C. (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - "Programme of the Young Communist International" (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - "Program of the Communist International", December, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - The Communist, June 12, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - "The Truth About the American Youth Congress", By Arthur Clifford, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - "15th National Student Congress, August 19- August 30, 1962" (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - "Our Generation Will Not Be Silent!", September, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - "You've Got a Right", Defending Democracy, By Sasha Small, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - "American Youth Acts", The Story of the American Youth Congress, By William W. Hinckley (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - "How Fare Youth?", By Tom Dennison (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - "Towards An American Student Union" (Box 158)
  - "Students Take A Stand", An Account of Student Conferences in Washington During Christmas Week, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Building a Militant Student Movement", Program of the National Student League (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "The American Youth Congress", What It Is, How It Works (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "For a New Youth Organization Dedicated to Education in the Spirit of Socialism!", by Leon Wofsy (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Our Generation is in Danger" (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Youth Fights for Peace, Jobs, Civil Rights" (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Youth Demands a Peaceful World", Report of the Second World Youth Congress (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Children Under Capitalism", By Grace Hutchins, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Dust Off Your Dreams", The Story of American Youth for Democracy (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America", July, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Class Unity, All-People's Unity- The Only Way", By Gus Hall, August, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Program For Victory" NY State Communist Party Election Platform, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sedition! To Protest and Organize against War Hunger and Unemployment, By J. Louis Engdahl, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Kodak Worker, V.1, N. 6, July 1928 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Kodak Worker, V.1, N. 8, September 1928 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Kodak Worker, V.1, N.11, January-February 1929 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "The Crisis in the Socialist Party", By William Z. Foster, November, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "The Path to Peace, Progress and Prosperity" (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Take a Stand for Peace, Jobs & Equality", June, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "The Reds in Dixie", Who Are the Communists and What Do They Fight For in the South?, By Tom Johnson, March, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "The Challenge to Labor", March, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - "New Program of the Communist Party U.S.A.", Ma, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America", April, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "On the Road to Bolshevization", 1929 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "AFL Upsurge Challenges Policies of Old Guard", By Leon Kaplan, April 18-19, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - "Security with FDR", By Vito Marcantonio, September, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - "The Real Huey P. Long", By Sender Garlin, May, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - "The Big Tax Swindle and How to Stop It", An Analysis and Program for Action, May, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - "Who are the Americans?", By Earl Browder, July, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - "Unite for Peace, Negro Freedom, Labor's Advance, Socialism", Resolutions of the 18th National Convention of the Communist Party, U.S.A., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - "Shall the Communist Party Change Its Name?", February, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - "Teheran and America", By Earl Browder, January, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "Teheran, Our Path in War and Peace", By Earl Browder, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "Draft Resolution for the 16th National Convention of the Communist Party, U.S.A.", Adopted Sept. 13, 1956, September, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - "The United States in Crisis- The Communist Solution", September, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - "Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America", October, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - "Constitution of the Communist Political Association" (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - "Draft Main Political Resolution", An Assessment and a Production, January, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "What New York State Needs", By The Communist Political Association of New York State (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - "Let's Pull Together for Jobs, Security, Democracy, and Peace", By Carl Ross, September, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - "The American Way to Jobs, Peace, and Democracy", Draft Program of the Communist Party, March, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - "What America Faces", The New War Danger and the Struggle for Peace, Democracy and Economic Security, By Eugene Dennis, March, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - "America at the Crossroads: Postwar Problems and Communist Policy", By Eugene Dennis, December, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - "The Struggle for Detente", By Gus Hall (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - "What America Needs", A Communist View, By Eugene Dennis and John Gates, March, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - "1977 The Year of the Press", By Mike Zagarell, January, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - "Make Your Dreams Come True", By Gil Green, June, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "The Youth and the Russian Revolution" (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - "The People Against the Trusts", Build a Democratic Front to Defeat Reaction Now and Win a People's Victory in 1948, By Eugene Dennis, December, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - The Communist International, Vol. XIV, No. 12, December, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - "World Voices on the Moscow Trials", A Compilation from the Labor and Liberal Press of the World, October 22, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - "Regional Autonomy for the Southwest", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - The Party Review (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - "The Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America" (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - "Main Political Resolution adopted by the 16th National Convention of the Communist Party, U.S.A.", February 9-12, 1957, April, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - "Fundamentals of Communism" (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - "Call to 16th National Convention Communist Party, U.S.A.", February 9-12, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - "The Communists Take a New Look", Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, U.S.A., By Eugene Dennis, May, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - "The Heritage of the Communist Political Association", By Robert Minor, August, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - "The Carter Administration's African Policy", By Henry Winston (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - "The Communist Party- 'The mind, the will and the honor of the working class!'", By James E. Jackson (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - "21 Questions About War and Peace", By Eugene Dennis, August, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - A Letter from the Communist Party of Los Angeles County, May, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - "The Communist Party", Vanguard Fighter for Peace, Democracy, Security, and Socialism, By Pettis Perry, April, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - "Communists and the People", Summation Speech to the Jury in the Second Foley Square Smith Act Trial of Thirteen Communist Leaders, By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, May, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - "Pattern for American Fascism", By John L. Spivak, September, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - "The Fascist Danger and How to Combat it", By Eugene Dennis, August, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - "Theory and Practice of the Communist Party", November, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - "The Red Baiting Racket and How it Works", By George Morris, October, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - "Is Communism Un-American?", 9 Questions About the Communist Party Answered, By Eugene Dennis, March, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - "Let the People Know", The Truth About the Communists Which the Un-American Committee Tried to Suppress, By Eugene Dennis, April, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - "The Red-Baiters Menace America", By Eugene Dennis, October, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - "Meet the Communists", By Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, March, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - "Communists and the Trade Unions", By Roy Hudson, October, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - "Communism Versus Fascism", By William Z. Foster, June, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Young Communist Review, November, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - "Party Organizer" (5), October 1937, April-June, 1938 and August, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - "Hague over Jersey" (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - "Who are the Reds?", By Roy Hudson, June, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - "Beat the Steel Crisis! Save Every Job!", By Gus Hall (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - "The Trotsky Opposition", Its Significance for American Workers, By Bertram D. Wolfe, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Socialism, What's In It For You, By A.B. Magil, April, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - "The Little Red Diary" No.1, Trade Unions in America, By W.Z. Foster, J.P. Cannon, and E.R. Browder, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - "The Russian Constitution", Adopted July 10, 1918, January 4, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - "Why Communism?", Plain Talks on Vital Problems, By M.J. Olgin, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - "The Truth About Communism!", 1930 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Frontiers, October 1931 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Frontiers, January 1932 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Frontiers, April 1932 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Frontiers, June 1932 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Frontiers, November 1932 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - "Who Are the Young Pioneers" Martha Campion, October 1943 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - "Meet the Communists", 1943 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - "The People's Demands" Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - "A Guide to the Club, Its Role in Building the United Front in 1950", A Handbook for Community Club Officers, Prepared By Carl Dorfman (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - "Unity or Else..." (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - The Student Advocate, February 1936 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - The Student Advocate, March 1936 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - The Student Advocate, May 1936 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - The Student Advocate, October-November 1936 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Student Review, December 1933 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Student Review, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Student Review, April 1935 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Student Review, October 1935 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - General View of the 1st Annual National Communist Veterans Encampment at Turner's Arena, May 8, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - "Motion Picture Workers: Keep Your Eye on the Ball The Eight Ball You Are Behind It!" Pamphlet, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - New Foundations, V. VI, N. 4, June 1953 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Equal Justice, Fall 1941 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - "Economic Questions, Commentary", 1952 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - "The Soviet Union", Your Questions Answered, By Margaret Cowl, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - "Agents of Peace" Pamphlet, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - The Gil Green League Building Bulletin (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - California's Brown Book, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - "The Mexican People of the Southwest", August 3 1948 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - "Men in Overalls, The Danger is Real- the Danger is Now!, You Can Make Truman Veto the Un-American Anti-Labor...Taft-Hartley Slave Bill!, You Can Also Force Blakney, Vandenberg, and Ferguson to Support a Veto" (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - 15 Years of the Communist Party, By Alex Bittelman, August, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - City College and War, Why were Twenty-one Students Expelled?, October, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Beware of the War Danger!, Stop, Look, and Listen!, By William Z. Foster, April, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - "Everything for Unity and Victory", By William Schneiderman (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - The Kefauver Committee and the Pete Panto Murder, By Michael Singer, May, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Youth Unity for Peace Against Militarization (Box 4, Folder 121)